<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingText</string>
    <string name="article_title">Battles Authology</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Behind that locked door</string>
    <string name="article_text">Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some datNow when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, www.flipkart.com automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
a is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
Now when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In ordeNow when you open New Tab, youll also see sites we think might be interesting to you. Some may be suggested by Mozilla or sponsored by one of our partners.

    In order to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon
r to provide this service, some data is automatically sent back to us in accordance with our Privacy Notice. You can turn this off by unchecking the option under the gear icon

    </string>
</resources>